Narrator: 1
A: Good afternoon.
How can I help you?
B: I have a reservation for five nights.
A: What’s your name?
B: Wayne Roberts.
A: How do you spell your first name?
B: W-A-Y-N-E.
A: Just a moment.
Narrator: 2
A: So, the sofa is eight hundred and ninety-nine pounds and ninety-nine in total.
What’s the address for delivery?
Is it a London address?
B: Yes, it’s in south London.
A: What’s the postcode?
B: It’s S-E twenty-one eight G-P.
A: And the address is…?
B: Fourteen Dangerford Road, flat two.
That’s in Forest Hill, London.
Narrator: 3
A: Welcome to our mobile phone helpline.
Please say the number of the mobile phone you have a problem with.
B: Oh seven seven oh-oh, nine oh-oh, seven eight two.
Narrator: 4
A: Now, every Friday I’m going to give you some writing to do
for homework at the weekend.
You can either give it to me in class on the Monday, or you can send it to me by email.
I’m going to give you my email address and I’d like you to write it down. OK?
It’s J-V-I-N-E-sixty-four dot Z-Y-X at O-U-P dot com.
B: Can you repeat that, please?
A: Yes, J-V-I-N-E-sixty-four dot Z-Y-X at O-U-P dot com.
Now, I’m going to write it on the board for you.
Did you get it right?
Well done.
Remember, this symbol is called at in English, and this one is dot.
Narrator: 5
A: Good evening.
B: Hi. We have a table booked for seven thirty.
A: Yes, madam. What name please?
B: Ann Rathbone.
R-A-T-H-B-O-N-E.
A: Ah, yes, here we are.
Can you come this way please?
Narrator: 6
A: OK, Susannah, that’s great.
Here’s your student card.
Your classes start on Monday at nine a.m.
Now, the classes are not here in the main school, but in a different building.
B: Oh?
A: But it’s very near, just five minutes’ walk from here, in Russell Street.
B: Sorry, what’s the address?
A: It’s sixteen Russell Street.
That’s R-U-double S-E-double L.
Let me show you on your phone.
B: Thank you.